- ConversationTopicId: 09A_M1_Topic_Morgaine
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M1_Topic_Morgaine_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M1_Topic_Morgaine_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09A_M1_Topic_Morgaine2
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M1_Topic_Morgaine2_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M1_Topic_Morgaine2_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M1_Topic_Trahern
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M1_Topic_Trahern_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M1_Topic_Trahern_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M1_Topic_Hargest
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M1_Topic_Hargest_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M1_Topic_Hargest_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M1_Topic_Eldred
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M1_Topic_Eldred_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M1_Topic_Eldred_TalkTo_next_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M2_Topic_Hargest
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M2_Topic_Hargest_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M2_Topic_Hargest_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M2_Topic_Oakes
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M2_Topic_Oakes_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M2_Topic_Oakes_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M2_Topic_Oakes2
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M2_Topic_Oakes2_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M2_Topic_Oakes2_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M2_Topic_Yoon_A
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M2_Topic_Yoon_A_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M2_Topic_Yoon_A_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M2_Topic_Yoon_B
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M2_Topic_Yoon_B_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M2_Topic_Yoon_B_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09A_M2_Topic_Morgaine
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M2_Morgaine_Talkto_topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M2_Morgaine_Talkto_topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M3_Topic_Trahern
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M3_Topic_Trahern_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M3_Topic_Trahern_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M3_Topic_Hargest
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M3_Topic_Hargest_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M3_Topic_Hargest_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M3_Topic_Hargest2
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M3_Topic_Hargest2_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M3_Topic_Hargest2_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M4_Topic_Riches
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M4_Riches_Topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M4_Riches_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M5_Topic_Trahern
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M5_Trahern_FL_Topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M5_Trahern_FL_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M5_Topic_Riches
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M5_Riches_TalkTo_Topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M5_Riches_TalkTo_Topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M6_Topic_Fionn
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M6_Fionn_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M6_Fionn_TalkTo_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M6_Topic_Ramla
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M6_Ramla_TalkTo_topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M6_Ramla_TalkTo_topic0"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M6_Josephine_Rescue
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M6_Josephine_Rescue_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M6_Josephine_Rescue_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M6_Vachon_Rescue
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M6_Vachon_Rescue_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M6_Vachon_Rescue_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M6_Zayden_Rescue
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M6_Zayden_Rescue_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M6_Zayden_Rescue_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M7_Josephine_Wires
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M7_Josephine_Wires_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M7_Josephine_Wires_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M7_Josephine_Thanks
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M7_Josephine_Thanks_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M7_Josephine_Thanks_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M8_Topic_Taurus
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_M8_Taurus_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_M8_Taurus_TalkTo_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M9_Topic_Shirzad
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_Shirzad_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_Shirzad_TalkTo_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M10_Topic_Kurok
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_Kurok_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_Kurok_TalkTo_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M11_Topic_Taurus
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M11_Taurus_TalkTo_topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M11_Taurus_TalkTo_topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M11_Topic_Shirzad
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M11_Shirzad_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M11_Shirzad_TalkTo_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M12_Topic_Taurus
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_Taurus_HG_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_Taurus_HG_TalkTo_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M13_Topic_Morgaine
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_Morgaine_SE_TalkTo_topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_Morgaine_SE_TalkTo_topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M14_Topic_Trahern1
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M14_Trahern_SE_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M14_Trahern_SE_TalkTo_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M14_Topic_Trahern2
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M14_Trahern_SE_TalkTo_2_topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M14_Trahern_SE_TalkTo_2_prompt"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M14_Topic_Trahern3
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M14_Trahern_LC_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M14_Trahern_LC_TalkTo_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M14_Topic_Morgaine
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M14_Morgaine_LC_TalkTo_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M14_Morgaine_LC_TalkTo_next"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M15_Topic_Morgaine
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M15_Morgaine_EP_TalkTo_topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M15_Morgaine_EP_TalkTo_topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M15_Topic_Morgaine2
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M15_Morgaine_EP_TalkTo_2_topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M15_Morgaine_EP_TalkTo_2_topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_M15_Topic_Artemis
  PlayerPrompt: "@09A_M15_Artemis_EP_TalkTo_topic_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09A_M15_Artemis_EP_TalkTo_topic"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_S0_Topic_Eldred
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_S0_Topic_Eldred_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_S0_Topic_Eldred_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_S17_Topic_Treadwell
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_S17_Topic_Treadwell_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_S17_Topic_Treadwell_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_S17_Topic_Treadwell2
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_S17_Topic_Treadwell2_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_S17_Topic_Treadwell2_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 09a_S17_Topic_Hargest
  PlayerPrompt: "@09a_S17_Topic_Hargest_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@09a_S17_Topic_Hargest_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
